savingsloans.com.au 2002-12-06

# Savings & Loans Credit Union - Privacy

Privacy and Security

Your use of the Savings & Loans Credit Union (S.A.) Ltd ('Savings & Loans Credit Union') website is governed by the Website Privacy Statement set out below.

Please read this information carefully. The use of this website by you indicates an acceptance of and agreement to be bound by the Privacy statement set out below. If you do not agree with the statement please do not use this website. Savings & Loans Credit Union reserves the right to make changes to this website and to this statement at any time. Any such modifications will become effective upon the date they are first posted to the website.

  1. **Website Privacy Statement for Savings & Loans Credit Union**

Any information that you provide to Savings & Loans Credit Union through this website will be maintained in accordance with this website privacy statement. Please ensure that you read the statement carefully and understand the purposes that information provided to Savings & Loans Credit Union will be collected used or disclosed. Savings & Loans Credit Union may change this statement from time to time and if so, Savings & Loans Credit Union will use reasonable efforts to publish such changes.

  2. **Anonymous use of this website**

When you browse this website you will do so anonymously. Personal information, such as your name, address, telephone number or email address is not collected. Savings & Loans Credit Union does, however, use 'cookies' to collect information about how the website is used. 

  3. **How does Savings & Loans Credit Union use cookies?**

"Cookies" give users a unique, random ID by storing small text files onto a user's computer hard drive with the user's browsers. Cookies enable a website to track a user's activities on a website. For example, Savings & Loans Credit Union may use cookies on its home page to keep a record of all visits to the website. This is an example of how Savings & Loans Credit Union may use cookies. Savings & Loans Credit Union may use cookies in other areas on its website now and in the future.

Savings & Loans Credit Union cookies do not contain personally identifying information. Users are free to change their web browsers to prevent the acceptance of cookies.

  4. **What information does Savings & Loans Credit Union gather from users of this website?**

Savings & Loans Credit Union may gather information from you including your name and address among other personal data. Savings & Loans Credit Union limits the collection of information from you to what is needed to provide its products and services, to offer new products and services, and to fulfil any legal and regulatory requirements. For more information in relation to the collection use and disclosure of information by Savings & Loans Credit Union please read the 'Your Privacy' Brochure. 

Information that is essential to the provision of services or products will be indicated as such on this website. All other information requested is additional information that provides Savings & Loans Credit Union with flexibility in the provision of services. For example a fax number may not be essential but will provide Savings & Loans Credit Union with another means of communication with you. 

The choice of how much personally identifiable information you disclose to Savings & Loans Credit Union is completely at your discretion. Savings & Loans Credit Union will advise of the general uses of information in this privacy statement and will provide additional explanation to you, if requested. Further information is contained in the Savings & Loans Credit Union 'Your Privacy' and 'Privacy FAQ' Brochures. Our fundamental concern is that you control the use of your own personal information. To this end, it is not mandatory for you to answer any questions, although in some circumstances if you choose to not answer questions it may limit the services and products Savings & Loans Credit Union is able to offer. 

  5. **How does Savings & Loans Credit Union use information collected from this website?**

In providing personal information to Savings & Loans Credit Union you are agreeing to allow Savings & Loans Credit Union to use the personal information you submit for any purposes related to Savings & Loans Credit Union's business, including but not limited to generating statistical studies, conducting market research, improving its products and services, sending new surveys and notifying you of new products, special offers, seminars and conventions and any other changes within Savings & Loans Credit Union that may affect you. Savings & Loans Credit Union may combine the information it obtains from this website with information that it already holds.

If you wish to limit the use of your personal information to purposes other than those outlined in these paragraphs you should advise Savings & Loans Credit Union in writing as soon as possible.

  6. **What choices do you have about how your personal information collected on this website is used and what is Savings & Loans Credit Union's commitment to data quality and reliability?**

Savings & Loans Credit Union respects your privacy and realises that not everyone likes to receive special offers or information. If you would like your name deleted from Savings & Loans Credit Union's list or if you don't want to receive Savings & Loans Credit Union 's email bulletins, please use the contact information below to request that Savings & Loans Credit Union remove you from its list. Be sure to include your name, postal address, telephone number, information contained in the Savings & Loans Credit Union mailer and/or other necessary information requested for removal. If you believe that Savings & Loans Credit Union may not have your correct and current personal information, please update your information by using the contact information below to inform Savings & Loans Credit Union of changes in your personal information.

  7. **What is Savings & Loans Credit Union's commitment to data security for this website?**

Savings & Loans Credit Union recognises your concern for security, and will use reasonable efforts to establish secure connections with you and to limit access to databases containing personal information to authorised personnel only.

Your information will be processed using the Web Site Trust Services provided by VeriSign. For more information see [www.verisign.com](http://www.verisign.com/)

  8. **Links with other Websites**

You should be aware that if you link to another website it may contain a privacy statement different from this statement and other terms and conditions may apply. 

  9. **Does this Website Privacy Statement refer to non-website interactions between you and the Savings & Loans Credit Union?**

This Website Privacy Statement is intended to relate only to information that is collected from you while you are using this website. The Savings & Loans Credit Union privacy policy for the collection use and disclosure of personal or sensitive information by the Savings & Loans Credit Union during non-website interactions is outlined in the Savings & Loans Credit Union 'Your Privacy' Brochure. This brochure will also provide you with important information in relation to the handling of, and access to your personal information. We suggest that you read the 'Your Privacy' and the 'Privacy FAQ' Brochures to obtain further information, however we invite you at any time to make further inquiries with Savings & Loans Credit Union in relation to Privacy.

Although Savings & Loans Credit Union consider that no inconsistency exists between this Website Privacy Statement and its other privacy policies, in the event of an inconsistency this Website Privacy Statement will take precedent for any information collected from the use of this website by you. In any other circumstances, the Savings & Loans Credit Union privacy policies apply equally.

  10. **What are Savings & Loans Credit Union's contact procedures?**

If you believe Savings & Loans Credit Union has not adhered to its privacy statement, if you would like to be removed from Savings & Loans Credit Union's lists, or if you would like to update your personal information, you may notify Savings & Loans Credit Union by e-mail, telephone, fax, or postal mail. Savings & Loans Credit Union will use reasonable efforts to promptly resolve any issues.  
**  
**

  11. **Who can I contact if I have concerns about privacy?**

Savings & Loans Credit Union would welcome comments by you in relation to privacy issues generally, or any privacy issues that concern you. You may also contact the Privacy Commissioner if you want to know more about privacy issues. Their web address is: http://www.privacy.gov.au

  12. **Savings & Loans Credit Union Contact Information**

Savings & Loans Credit Union (S.A.) Ltd  
50 Flinders Street   
Adelaide S.A. 5000  
Telephone: 13 11 82 or (08) 8305 8305  
Facsimile: (08) 8305 8318

Savings & Loans Credit Union has also made it convenient for you to be removed from Savings & Loans Credit Union's e-mail bulletins. Just go to Contact Us. 

Your Privacy

The protection of your privacy is very important to us. Download the 'Your Privacy' brochure for further information.

**Your Privacy brochure** (File size = 91 kb)   

Frequently Asked Questions

We have developed a Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ) brochure to provide you with an understanding of our privacy policy in relation to the management of personal information.

**FAQ brochure** (File size = 57kb)
